CURRICULUM VITAE

NAME: KISIA GODWILL TREVOR

PHONE NO.: +254726739857

ID NUMBER: 37033644

EMAIL ADDRESS: godwillkisia5@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a passionate and proficient software developer with over four years of experience in developing web and android applications using various technologies. I have a strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL, MongoDB, Postgres, Flutter, JavaScript, Nodejs, Java, Python as well as frameworks such as Laravel, Flask, Django and Vue.js. I have successfully delivered projects for clients in various industries, National Intelligence Service, Department of Defence and done my own projects in Agriculture such as The Smart Dairy Application. I enjoy learning new tools and techniques to improve my coding skills and create user-friendly solutions.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

September 2018-Present: Egerton University Bachelor of Science in

computer Science

2013-2017: Mudasa secondary school *K.C.S.E (B+)*

2005-2012: Sunrise Valley Academy K.C.P.E (382) marks

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP

KENYA POWER

January 2023 – present

Duties and responsibilities

- Software installation.
- Hardware troubleshooting.
- Fibre termination.
- Cable maintenance.
- Fibre splicing.
- System configuration.

- Network troubleshooting.
- Data entry.

INTERNSHIP

BLUERAY COMPANY

January 2018- August 2018

Duties and responsibilities

- Drafting reports on the progress of project development stages.
- Software development.
- Integrating postgres database with blutics.
- Developing Text Clustering module for BigBlue.
- Creating GIS and Mapping module for Blutics.
- CDR Analysis (Blutics) integration with BigBlue.
- Development of Blutics(Call Data Record) analysis tool for crime detection and prevention.

SKILLS

- Python
- Flask
- Django
- Java
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- PHP
- Android using flutter and java
- C, C++
- Sql
- Database management.
- Software installation.
- Network troubleshooting.
- Hardware troubleshooting.
- Network Security

PROJECTS DONE

- Blutics (Call Data Records) analysis tool under the department of defence and National Intelligence Service.
- Big Blue for intelligence tool for the department of defence and National Defence Service.
- Smart Dairy System (Android and web based system)

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Awarded certificate of participation 2016 by Kenya Secondary Schools Students Council
- Awarded certificate of participation by Raise Your Game Leadership Training Programme 2016

CLUBS AND SOCIETIES

- Debate Club
- Straight Talk Club (guidance and counselling)
- Egerton University Computer Science Association (EUCOSA)

LEADERSHIP

- Deputy school captain high school level
- House captain high school level
- Class representative high school level
- Class representative primary school level

OBJECTIVES

- To apply my abilities and experience in the service of humanity by providing leadership and new approaches in confronting challenges and seizing opportunities.
- To add value to the organization by applying myself to challenging work environments that will enhance my knowledge in the field of computer science and other fields as I pursue my career
- To be keen on opportunities that will expose me to business and other working opportunities.

REFEREES

1. Mr. Sanjeet Thethy

C.E.O Bluray Company 0723134242

2. Dr. Bosire Omariba

Lecturer Egerton University +254729154296

3. Mrs. Velma O. Madanye

The principal, Mudasa Secondary school 0722890896